buzzmixer.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy

Buzzmixer www.buzzmixer.com protects all the data and information that you provide to us. We ensure that your privacy is protected. The submission of your personal information is not required in order to browse BuzzMixer.

However, privacy policies are subjected to change without prior information.

Security of personal information:

We commit you a safe receipt of your shared information. To protect any illegal tasks we use industry’s best standard measures. We do not disclose personal information to others without your approval other than some specific incidents:

  * In order to take any action against suspected illegal activities/ violation of the our terms and provisions
  * To enforce or entail terms and conditions and privacy policies
  * To protect our status, assets and our rights/ rights of third party and personal safety of the users
  * We may also disclose personal information if it is required by the law to do so in a good belief.
  * In case of transferring or selling the website to other company user info will be transferred too. We may disclose non-identifiable data to third parties which don't include your name, email address or contact number.

**Other websites links:**

The content on this website may contain links to other external websites. Once you will click on such links they will redirect you to other websites. Please acknowledge the fact that we do not have any control over that particular website(s). Therefore, we are not responsible for the privacy and security of the information whilst you visit these sites.

**What data we collect**

We can receive your information automatically through our web server, which includes computer ID, information obtained from “cookies”, alternate email ID, financial information, age, the domain server through which you access our service, and IP address.

We may also collect following personal information about you: Name, Mobile phone, and other contact details, ZIP/Postal code, the links you click on our site and the number of times you accessed our page. In case you connect with BuzzMixer via social networking sites like Facebook, Twitter, Google+ etc we can store your personal information you have chosen to display in those networks. Further, in case you send or receive personal messages to another user of BuzzMixer, we can record all messages that you send or receive.

**Note:**  We respect our visitors/users rights and support “Right to be forgotten”. If you think you’ve ever shared your contact details with us & want us to remove that info, please contact us at [info@buzzmixer.com](mailto:info@buzzmixer.com)

**Cookies on BuzzMixer**

BuzzMixer Inc. (we, our or us) uses cookies, web beacons and similar technologies on www.buzzmixer.com to function efficiently. With this notice, we provide you with information about the cookies used on site, their purpose and choices you can make with regard to the use of cookies.

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small files that may be placed on your computer’s hard drive through your web browser when you access a website. Buzzmixer make use of cookies to enable our servers to recognize your web browser. A web beacon is also known as an internet tag, clear GIF, and pixel tag.

**Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics to track visitors on this site. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect this data.In order to be compliant with the new regulation Google included a data processing amendment.The data we collect will be processed anonymously and “Data sharing” is disabled.We don’t use other Google services in combination with Google Analytics cookies.
